Guide to the Brooklyn Arts Council Folk Arts collection CBHM.0002
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 3: Brooklyn Maqam Arab Music Festival
  - Sub-series 3.2: Audiovisual
    Arab-o-Rama, March 14, 2008, Eddie Kochak
    Arab-o-Rama, March 14, 2008, Scott Wilso
    - Interviews, Audio, 2008 (Box 41, Item 1-9)
    - Performances, Audio, 2008 (Box 41, Item 10-42)
    - Events, Audio, 2008 (Box 41, Item 43-50)
    - Publicity, 2008 (Box 41, Item 51-54)
    - Photographs, 2008 (Box 42, Item 1-13)
    - Performers, Commercial and Demo, Not Progam, 1987 (Box 42, Item 14)
    - Performers, Commercial and Demo, Not Program, circa 1990-2008 (Box 42, Item 15-42)
    - Performers, Commercial and Demo, Not Program, circa 1990-2008 (Box 43, Item 1-12)
    - Performers, Demo Recordings, VHS, 2008 (Box 43, Item 13-14)
- Series 4: Days of the Dead in Brooklyn
  Days of the Dead in Brooklyn: Diverse Traditions of Death, Dying and Renewal was a year-long project begun in September 2008 to acquaint the public with traditional arts, rituals and customs used to address the deaths of family and community members in Brooklyn. The project included field research, documentation and 12 public programs (5 concert/performances, 7 lectures/demonstrations/workshops/symposia) held throughout Brooklyn from September 2008-June 2009. Over 1,400 people attended DoDB events and 160 artists participated in the initiative.
  The goals for the project were to heighten awareness of traditional arts practices related to death through engaging public programs and field research activities, to bridge the gap between diverse communities and health care systems, and to work toward a model for integrating traditional arts practices relating to death into public programming and health care practices.
  Program Files include correspondence, event-related materials, publicity, funding, and financial information. Also included are research materials, which encompass press clippings, event flyers, and related items about topics explored during the course of the project and to the death and dying traditions of various cultural groups. Audiovisual documentation includes digital photographs, recordings of events, as well as performances of funerary songs and a series of interviews with Brooklyn funeral directors.
  Days of the Dead in Brooklyn events included:
  Mexican Days of the Dead How to prepare a Mexican Days of the Dead ofrenda, a traditional altar to honor the dead. Sunset Park Library, October 28, 2008.
  Mexican Days of the Dead Preparing sugar skulls and paper flowers for an ofrenda. Sunset Park Library, October 29, 2008.
  All Soul's Day: Symbols, Stories and Trumpets A gravesite tour of Green-Wood Cemetery and a Haitian rara graveyard procession, November 2, 2008.
  Prayers for the Dead Concert highlighting a variety of culturally specific funerary musical traditions, including Jewish, Italian, Buddhist and African-Grenadian. Congregation Beth Elohim, November 23, 2009.
  Undertaking Death: A Conversation with Brooklyn Funeral Directors Featuring local undertakers providing insight into the folklore of death and remembrance as practiced in Russian, Polish, Lebanese and Dominican communities. Brooklyn Public Library, Grand Army Plaza, Dweck Auditorium, May 20, 2009.
  Understanding Traditional Arts and Death and Dying, June 16-23, 2009.
  Diverse Traditions of Death and Dying in Brooklyn A kick-off symposium/arts demonstration presenting discussion and performance from funeral directors and traditional artists. Brooklyn Historical Society, September 21, 2008.
  Ofrenda Altar and Chinese Buddhist Ancestral Altar Dedication Sunset Park Library, November 1, 2008.
  Folk Feet 6th Annual Traditional Dance Showcase Trinidadian limbo, Chinese folk dancers, Turkish mevlid, rural Dominican funerary processional, classical Indian dance, Grenadian bongo, South Korean funerary procession, excerpts of Greek Orthodox memorial service hymn. Brooklyn College Center for the Performing Arts, Whitman Theater, March 1, 2009.
  Virgin of Sorrows Procession Sacred Hearts and St. Stephen Church, Carroll Gardens, April 10, 2009.
  Waking the Dead: Afro-Caribbean Funerary Expressions Featuring traditional artists, scholars and funeral directors exploring pan-Caribbean mourning traditions. Brooklyn Public Library Flatbush Branch, April 23, 2009.
  - Sub-series 4.1: Program Files
    - Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Notes, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Audience Contacts, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Factsheet, Tell Us Your Traditions, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Kick Off Symposium, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Workshop I: Mexican Days of the Dead, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Workshop II: Mexican Days of the Dead, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Ofredna Altar and Chinese Buddhist Ancestral Altar Dedication, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - All Soul's Day "Symbols, Stories and Trumpets" at Green-Wood Cemetery, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Prayers for the Dead, 2008 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Folk Feet Dance Showcase, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Virgin of Sorrows Procession, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Waking the Dead, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Undertaking Death, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Understanding Traditional Arts of Death and Dying, 2009 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Postcards and Posters, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Oversize Posters, 2008 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - BAC News, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Funding, NEA, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Funding, NYS Tribute Foundation, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Funding Notes, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Check Requests and W-9 Forms, Artist Fees, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Invoices and Check Requests, Administrative, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Unpaid, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Research, Animal and Pet Death, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Research, Artists, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Research, Books, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Research, Cemeteries, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Research, Facing Death, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Research, Funeral Home Directors in Bklyn, History, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Research, Funeral Home Related- Caskets, Hearses, 2008-2009 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Research, Ghost Stories, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Research, Gravestones, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Research, Halloween and Dia de los Muertos, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Research, Healthcare and Death, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Research, Memorials, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Research, Misc., 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Research, el Museo del Barrio, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Research, Performance of Death, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Research, Veterans, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Research, Witchcraft and Death, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Research, Traditions, African American and Legacy of African Traditions in the South (Gullah People), 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Research, Traditions, Afro-Caribbean Funeral and Mourning, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Research, Traditions, Asian, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Research, Traditions, Asian Display Materials, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Research, Traditions, Asian Display Materials, 2009 (Cabinet Morgue Flat File 1, Drawer 8)
    - Research, Traditions, Berawan (in Sarawak, Malaysia), 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Research, Traditions, Buddhist, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Research, Traditions, Jewish Funeral and Mourning, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Research, Traditions, Latino / South American, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Research, Traditions, Middle Eastern, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Research, Traditions, Muslim Turkish (Includes Merlid), 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Research, Traditions, Wiccan, 2008-2009 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Sub-series 4.2: Audiovisual
    Events represented in the Audiovisual sub-series include:
    Diverse Traditions of Death and Dying in Brooklyn. A kick-off symposium/arts demonstration presenting discussion and performance from funeral directors and traditional artists. Brooklyn Historical Society, September 21, 2008.
    Ofrenda Altar and Chinese Buddhist Ancestral Altar Dedication. Sunset Park Library, November 1, 2008.
    Virgin of Sorrows Procession. Sacred Hearts and St. Stephen Church, Carroll Gardens, April 10, 2009.
    Waking the Dead: Afro-Caribbean Funerary Expressions. Featuring traditional artists, scholars and funeral directors exploring pan-Caribbean mourning traditions. Brooklyn Public Library Flatbush Branch, April 23, 2009.
    Interviews with funeral directors:
    Erham Yildirim
    Keith Sento
    James Donofrio
    - Events, Audio, 2009 (Box 46, Item 1-15)
    - Events, Video, 2009 (Box 46, Item 16-32)
    - Events, Photos, 2009 (Box 46, Item 33-39)
    - Event Related, 2009 (Box 46, Item 40-44)
    - Interviews, 2009 (Box 46, Item 45-54)
    - Related, 2009 (Box 46, Item 56)
- Series 5: Folk Feet: Celebrating Traditional Dance in Brooklyn
  Folk Feet: Celebrating Traditional Dance in Brooklyn, was a multi-year project led by Folk Arts Director Kay Turner. The project began in August 2003 and concluded in 2009 as a first-ever attempt to identify, document and present the range of traditional dance practices in Brooklyn. The project included several series of programs including an annual dance showcase at Brooklyn College, dance workshops, "Circle Round" focusing on circle or ring dances, professional development workshops, demonstrations, interviews, fieldwork, and symposia.
  Program Files include correspondence, publicity materials, and artist information, as well as print-outs from the Brooklyn Arts Council website about Folk Feet, and funding documentation. Audiovisual materials include raw and edited performance video, interviews with artist-participants, and photographs taken during events. Photographs are print and digital.
  Events represented in the Program Files and Audiovisual sub-series include:
  BCAT Promo, 2003.
  Conjunto Nuevo Milenio (Panamanian), October 9, 2003.
  Brighton Ballet Theater Nutcracker, December 13, 2003.
  Folk Feet: Celebrating Dance in Brooklyn, Brooklyn Center for the Performing Arts, undated.
  Brooklyn College (BCBC) showcase, February 20, 2004.
  The Danced Body in Brooklyn, April 6, 2004.
  Folk Feet Symposium, "Teaching Traditional Dance", June 19, 2004.
  Folk Feet at Fort Greene Park, Euston James and Maimouna Keita West African Dance Company, June 20, 2004.
  Folk Feet at Fort Greene Senior Center, undated.
  Redhawk Indian Arts Council Pow Wow, Floyd Bennett Field, June 20, 2004.
  Young Hoofers, August 14, 2004.
  Folk Feet Workshop, Brooklyn Public Library, October 10, 2004.
  St. Lucy's Feast, December 11, 2004.
  Al'e'mo Squares, December 12, 2004.
  BCBC -- Folk Feet: Celebrating Traditional Dance in Brooklyn, 2nd annual showcase, February 20, 2005.
  Folk Feet at Fort Greene Park: Rita Silva Los Bomeros de Brooklyn, The Young Hoofers, Yahya Kamate, June 19, 2005.
  Gowanus Wildcat Drill Team anniversary, June 30, 2005.
  Gowanus Wildcats, November 2005.
  Maimouna Keita, undated.
  Swedish Folkdancers of New York, Lincoln Center, 2005.
  Yemeni American Association, Lincoln Center, 2005.
  Folk Feet at Fort Greene Park, June 19, 2005.
  Arab-American Heritage Week in Prospect Park, July 20, 2005.
  Desfile Dominicano, August 5, 2005.
  Workshop, August 13, 2005.
  Lincoln Center Out of Doors Showcase: The World Dances in Brooklyn: Music and Dance on the Plaza, August 24, 2005.
  Gowanus Wildcats, 2005.
  Rita Silva, 2005.
  Young Hoofers, 2005.
  BCBC: Folk Feet, Celebrating Traditional Dance in Brooklyn, 3rd annual showcase, February 26, 2006.
  BCAT programming, 2006.
  Dance workshop, Brooklyn Public Library, March 5, 2006.
  Folk Feet symposium: Dance and the Diaspora: Professional Development Seminar, April 6, 2006.
  Lincoln Center Out of Doors: Playday!, August 5, 2006.
  Circle Round, Tobacco Warehouse, Brooklyn Bridge Park, Dumbo, October 8, 2006.
  Symposium: Conference on Research and Dance, November 2-5, 2006.
  Dance workshop/Teacher training: Footbridge workshop meeting, December 8, 2006.
  BCBC – Folk Feet, Celebrating Traditional Dance in Brooklyn, 4th annual dance showcase, March 11, 2007.
  Dance workshop: Brooklyn Public Library, March 18, 2007.
  Symposium: Congreso International Musica Identidad y Cultura en el Caribe, April 13-15, 2007.
  Symposium: Immigrant History Week, April 16-22, 2007.
  Foot Notes: Folk Feet Meet Modern Feet, April 18, 2009.
  Folk Feet West, at Pavilion Central School and Medina High School, April 28-29, 2007.
  Symposium: Managing an Artistic Life: A Conference for the Dance Community, June 11, 2007.
  Foot Notes: Folk Feet Meet Modern Feet, Yasser Darwish, Meredith Glisson, Katie Kei, Kevin "Shock-a-lock" Porter, Rita Silva. At Chez Bushwick, June 14, 2007.
  Circle Round 2, Fort Greene Park, June 17, 2007.
  Dance workshop/Teacher training: Footbridge workshops, Deborah Carr, Irish Dancing class, July 9, 2007.
  Lincoln Center Out of Doors: Playday Dance-In, August 4, 2007.
  Fight Night - Folk Feet/Solo Feet/DUMBO BID's Fight Night, September 20, 2007.
  Dance workshop/Teacher training: Partnering in Promotion, Long Island Traditions, September 24, 2007.
  Circle Round, Brooklyn Bridge Park, September 30, 2007.
  Fight Night, St. Ann's Warehouse, October 2, 2008.
  Symposium: American Folklore Society, October 17-18, 2007.
  Belen ara Pedro, Los Bomberos de Brooklyn, October 23, 2007.
  Symposium: Congress on Research and Dance, November 8-11, 2007.
  FFDW, Yasser Darwish, Saidi and Tannoor, November 17, 2007.
  NEST Bac-Bomba, November 21, 2007.
  Dance Workshop, Euston James, December 13, 2007.
  Dance Workshop/Teacher training, Kathleen Condon and Emily Socolov, Cultural context, January 5, 2008.
  Folk Feet on Fifth, February 7, 2008.
  Symposium: Immigrant History Week, April 2, 2008.
  Arab Dance Workshops and Panel, April 21-22, 2008.
  Circle Round 3, Fort Greene Park, June 8, 2008.
  Dance Workshop, Haitian Kompas, Breaking and Electric Boogie, June 8, 2008.
  Social Dance Traditions in the Arab World, July 13-20, 2008.
  Brooklyn Historical Society Collaboration – Shock-a-lock, August 6, 2008.
  Brooklyn Historical Society Collaboration, August 8, 2008.
  Brooklyn Historical Society Oral History Project, 2008.
  Folk Feet on Fifth – Holy Cross Street Festival – Greek Dance, September 29, 2008.
  Folk Feet on Fifth; Hoofin' It In the Hood: Neighborhood Dance Traditions of Sunset Park and Bay Ridge, Ocober 16, 2008.
  Symposium: Conference on Research in Dance, November 14-16, 2008.
  Dance workshop: Ukranian Folk Vechornytsi, November 20, 2008.
  Folk Feet on Fifth – Swedish Dance, December 15, 2008.
  Folk Feet on Fifth – Lebanese Dance, December 20, 2008.
  Brooklyn Maqam Beings: Traditional Arab Dance Showcase at BCBC, 2008.
  Folk Feet Training, 2008.
  Folk Feet on Fifth: January 2009 Dance Events, January 2009.
  Levantine Layali and Norwegian Nights, Jad Lebbos, Sheren Attal, Paul Busse, Ramzi Ed Libi, Abrahim Elehan, February 14, 2009.
  Folk Feet on Fifth – Chinese Dance in Sunset Park, February 1, 2009.
  Folk Feet Assembly, 2009.
  Lebanese Dance, 2009.
  Dance in the Neighborhood: Benito Bravo at Mexican Sunset Park Quinceanera; Nostrand Ave at Newkirk in Flatbush, 2009.
  Swedish Dance, February 15, 2009.
  BCBC Sixth Annual Traditional Dance Showcase, Ritual and Ceremonial Dance Traditions of Brooklyn, March 1, 2009.
  Fieldwork/Oral History Brooklyn Historical Society Collaboration: Donny Golden, Irish Dance Class in Bay Ridge, March 18, 2009.
  Symposium: Immigrant History Week, April 2, 2009.
  Dance workshop: Limbo, ancestral dance, April 15, 2009.
  Folk Feet on Fifth: Cumbia, Bomba, and Salsa in Sunset Park, April 24, 2009.
  Tour of Sunset Park: Kaluga, Benito Bravo, Brooklyn Chinese-American Association, LaGran Via Bakery, 5th Avenue Chinese Restaurant, Los Tres Polrillos, La Salsa de Hoy, May 2009.
  Circle Round Dance workshops, May 6, 2009.
  Folk Feet on Fifth: Bay Ridge by Night Neighborhood Tour, May 9, 2009.
  Conversations: Rediscovering Community Based Resources to Sustain Your Art, Professional Development Workshop, June 10, 2009
  Folk Feet West, June 12-14, 2009.
  Folk Feet Circle Round, Sunset Park: Indian, Mexican, Egyptian, Debleen, Korean, Afro-Dominican, Haitian, June 2009.
  See Audiovisual sub-series for a list of interviews.
  Due to sensitive personal information, materials in box 100, folder 5 are not open for research.
  - Sub-series 5.1: Program Files
    - Programs and Events, 2003-2009 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Dance Workshops, 2005 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - 3rd Annual Traditional Dance Showcase, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - 4th Annual Dance Showcase, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - 4th Annual Traditional Dance Showcase, Contracts, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Dance Workshops, Evaluations, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Arab Traditional Showcase, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - 6th Annual Traditional Dance Showcase, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Historical Society, Oral History Project, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Circle Round Brooklyn, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Circle Round, Evaluations, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Circle Round, Contracts and Check Requests, 2006 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Circle Round Brooklyn 2, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Circle Round, Empire, Fulton Ferry State Park, 2007 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Circle Round Brooklyn 3, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Circle Round Workshops and Performance, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Dance Meets, Arab Dance Workshop and Panel, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Dance Workshops, Brooklyn Public Library, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Dance Workshops, Brooklyn Public Library, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Dance Workshops, Evaluations and Thank you Notes, 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Dance Workshops, Social Dance Traditions from the Arab World, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Dance Workshops, Ukrainian Folk Vechornytsi, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Dance Workshops, Limbo: Ancestral Dance, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Evaluation Meeting, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Teacher Training, Footbridge Workshop Meeting, 2006 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Teacher Training, Footbridge Workshops, Deborah Carr, Irish Dancing Class, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Teacher Training, Partnering in Promotion, Long Island Traditions, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Teacher Training, Ana Nery Fragusu, Teaching to Youth, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Teacher Training, Notes, 2007-2008 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Teacher Training, Kathleen Condon and Emily Socolov, Cultural Context, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Teacher Training, Correspondence, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Teacher Training, Te Perez, Safe Dancing and Teaching, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Teacher Training, Check Requests, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Teacher Training, Insurance Waivers, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Folk Feet at Fort Greene Park, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Folk Feet on Fifth, Fieldwork, circa 2003-2008 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Folk Feet on Fifth, Hoofin' It in the Hood, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Folk Feet on Fifth, Cumbia, Bomba and Salsa in Sunset Park, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Folk Feet on Fifth, January 2009 Events (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Folk Feet on Fifth, Bay Ridge by Night Neighborhood Tour, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Folk Feet on Fifth, On Film, Permissions, 2008-2009 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - DUMBO Fight Night, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - DUMBO Fight Night, 2008 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Folk Feet Meet Modern Feet, Notes, 2009 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Lincoln Center Out of Doors, The World Dances in Brooklyn, Music and Dance on the Plaza, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Lincoln Center Out of Doors, Dance-In, 2007 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Folk Feet on Tour, Folk Feet West, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Folk Feet on Tour, Folk Feet West, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Professional Development, Dance in the Diaspora, Transformations and Continuities in Brooklyn Traditional Dance, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Professional Development, NYFA-BAC Conversations, Rediscovering Community Bases Resources to Sustain Your Art, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Professional Development, NYFA Mentoring Program for Immigrant Artists, 2008-2009 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Symposia, Folk Feet, The Danced Body in Brooklyn, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Symposia, Conference on Research in Dance, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Symposia, Congreso International Musica Identidad Y Cultura En El Caribe, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Symposia, Immigrant History Week, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Symposia, Managing an Artistic Life, A Conference for the Dance Community, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Symposia, American Folklore Society, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Symposia, Congress on Research and Dance, 2007 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Symposia, Immigrant History Week, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Symposia, Immigrant History Week, 2009 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Symposia, Conference on Research and Dance, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Archives, 2008 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Event Sign In Sheets, Name Tags, Artist Cards, circa 2003-2009 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Artists, Misc., circa 2003-2009 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Storycorps Video and Audio Recordings, Permissions, 2008-2009 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Fieldwork, Misc., circa 2003-2009 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Publicity, Contracts, circa 2003-2009 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Publicity, Flyers, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Publicity, Press Clippings, circa 2003-2009 (Box 49, Folder 23-24)
    - Publicity, Press Releases, circa 2003-2009 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Research, Immigration Theme, 2006 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Folk Feet on Fifth, Website as of 9/18/2009 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Folk Feet Main Pages, Website as of 9/18/2009 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Meet the Teachers, Website as of 9/18/2009 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Circle Round, Website as of 2009 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Dance Workshop (Chronological), Website as of 9/18/2009 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Dance Workshops, Cultural Traditions, Website as of 9/18/2009 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Funding, Budget, FY 2007 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Funding, Funder Acknowledgement Guidelines, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Funding, Notes, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Funding, Capezio/Ballet Makers Dance Foundation, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Funding, Century 21 for Folk Feet on Fifth, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Funding, Con Edison Strategic Partnerships, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Funding, Danskin, 2003-2005 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Funding, Emma A. Sheafer Charitable Trust for Footbridge Project, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Funding, M and T Bank, Bay Ridge for Folk Feet on Fifth, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Funding, Mertz-Gilmore Foundation for Footbridge Project, Correspondence and Reports, 2004-2008 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Funding, Mertz-Gilmore Foundation for Footbridge Project, Applications, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Funding, Mertz-Gilmore Foundation for Footbridge Project, Budgets and Financial Information, 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Funding, NEA, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Funding, NEA, 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Funding, NEA, 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Funding, NEA, Folk and Traditional Arts, Brooklyn Renaissance, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Funding, New York Community Trust, 2006-2009 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Funding, New York Community Trust for Footbridge Project, 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Funding, NYSCA, Final Report 2004 (Box 50, Folder 19)